{
  "minecraft-version": "Minecraft versio",
  "plugin-load-problem": "\"Modia {{plugin-name}} ei voida ladata\".",
  "pocketmine-version": "Pocketmine versio",
  "bedrock-version": "Bedrock versio",
  "forge-version": "Forge versio",
  "authme-shutdown-problem": "Plugin 'AuthMe' kaatuu lataamisessa ja sammuttaa serverin.",
  "pex-config-problem": "'PermissionEx' plugini ei ole käytettävissä.",
  "ambiguous-plugin-name-problem": "Löydetty kaksi samaa tiedostoa pluginille {} ':' {} ' and' {}.",
  "plugin-dependency-problem": "Plugini '{{plugin-name}}' tarvitsee plugini '{{dependency-plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-disabling-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' could not be disabled.",
  "plugin-enabling-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' could not be enabled.",
  "plugin-runtime-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' has a problem while running.",
  "forge-confirm-problem": "Forge tarvitsee sinun lupasi hyväksyä muutokset ja käynnistää serveri.",
  "mod-dependency-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' is missing the required mod {{dependency-mod-name}}.",
  "mod-dependency-problem-plural": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' is missing the required mods {{dependency-mod-list}}.",
  "mod-duplicate-problem": "There are multiple mod files for the mod name '{{mod-name}}': '{{first-mod-path}}' and '{{second-mod-path}}'.",
  "mod-exception-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' has thrown an exception.",
  "mod-fatal-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' has a fatal error.",
  "world-missing-mod-problem": "The world was saved with mod '{{mod-name}}' which appears to be missing.",
  "world-mod-version-problem": "This world was saved with mod '{{mod-name}}' version {{mod-expected-version}} and it is now at version {{mod-current-version}}.",
  "plugin-incompatible-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' is incompatible with your current server version.",
  "aquatic-world-on-older-version-problem": "Tämä maa on tallenettu/luotu minecraft 1.13 tai korkeammalla. Ja sinun versiosi ei tue tätä maata.",
  "old-player-directory-problem": "The server has detected an old player directory in the world save.",
  "command-run-solution": "Run the command '{{command}}'.",
  "authme-shutdown-solution": "Set 'stopServer' to 'true'.",
  "configure-plugin": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}}.",
  "configure-plugin-with-file": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}} ({{suggested-file}}).",
  "plugin-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different version of the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-install-solution": "Install the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-remove-solution": "Remove the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "file-delete-solution": "Delete the file '{{file-path}}'.",
  "file-edit-solution": "Edit the file '{{file-path}}'.",
  "mod-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different version of the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-install-solution": "Install the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-install-solution-with-version": "Install the mod '{{mod-name}}' with version {{mod-version}}.",
  "mod-remove-solution": "Remove the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "aquatic-version-install-solution": "Päivitä serverin versio.",
  "plugin-command-exception-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' cannot execute the command '{{command}}'.",
  "ticking-block-entity-problem": "A block in the world is causing problems.",
  "remove-block-solution": "Remove the block from the world, e.g. with MCEdit.",
  "do-nothing-solution": "Do nothing. This problem might fix itself.",
  "chunk-load-exception-problem": "There was an exception while loading the world chunks.",
  "remove-chunk-solution": "Remove the problematic chunk from the world, e.g. with MCEdit or by removing the region file.",
  "multiverse-load-problem": "The world '{{world-name}}' could not be loaded because it contains errors and is probably corrupt.",
  "world-repair-solution": "Repair the world '{{world-name}}', e.g. by using Minecraft Region Fixer or MCEdit.",
  "world-duplicate-problem": "World '{{world-name}}' is a duplicate of another world and has been prevented from loading.",
  "mod-wrong-minecraft-version-problem": "Mod {{mod-name}} 'ei ole yhteensopiva Minecraftin {{minecraft-version}} version kanssa.",
  "forge-install-different-version-solution": "Asenna eri forge versio.",
  "malformed-encoding-problem": "Jotain (mahdollisesti MOTD) sisältää virheellisiä muotokoodeja.",
  "change-motd-solution": "Vaihda serverin kuvaus."
}